sultan-center.com 2017-06-06

# TSC - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. The Sultan Center is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. The Sultan Center may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### SECTION I

**WHAT WE COLLECT**

WE MAY COLLECT THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### SECTION II 

**CONSENT**

How do you get my consent?

  * When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting your information and using it for that specific reason only.
  * If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.

### SECTION III 

**DISCLOSURE**

  * We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

### SECTION IV

**PAYMENT**

  * Currently we are only accepting _payment_ on delivery which can be in the form of cash, credit card payment or Knet payment as our Delivery agent has the payment machine with him at your doorstep. No payment data are stored at the website.

### SECTION V 

**THIRD - PARTYSERVICES**

  * In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.
  * However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
  * For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. 
  * In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you .So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
  * Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

### SECTION VII 

**AGE OF CONSENT**

By using this site, you represent that you are above the legal law to 21 years old and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.

### SECTION VIII

**SECURITY**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**HOW WE USE COOKIES**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**LIST OF COOKIES WE COLLECT**

The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.

COOKIE NAME

| 

COOKIE DESCRIPTION  
  
---|---  
  
CART

| 

The association with your shopping cart.  
  
CATEGORY_INFO

| 

Stores the category info on the page, which allows displaying pages more quickly.  
  
CUSTOMER

| 

An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_AUTH

| 

An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
  
CUSTOMER_INFO

| 

An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS

| 

Stores the Customer Segment ID  
  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE

| 

A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
  
FRONTEND

| 

You session ID on the server.  
  
GUEST-VIEW

| 

Allows guests to edit their orders.  
  
LAST_CATEGORY

| 

The last category you visited.  
  
LAST_PRODUCT

| 

The most recent product you have viewed.  
  
NO_CACHE

| 

Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART

| 

A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
  
POLL

| 

The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
  
POLLN

| 

Information on what polls you have voted on.  
  
STF

| 

Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
  
STORE

| 

The store view or language you have selected.  
  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE

| 

Indicates whether a customer allowed using cookies.  
  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS

| 

The products that you have recently viewed.  
  
WISHLIST

| 

An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
  
WISHLIST_CNT

| 

The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.

If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

Questions & Contact Information

If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer through [customer.support@sultan-center.com](mailto:ecomm-support@sultan-center.com) or visit us in person at The Sultan Center Headquarters.

[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]

[Updated: 03/07/2016]

[Sultan Bin Essa Complex, Building 44, Street 7, Block 1, Area 19, Dhajeej, FA, 13126, Kuwait]
